<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss xmlns:a10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Swrith</title><link>https://swrith.com/</link><description>Swrith Rss Feed</description><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright 2019</copyright><managingEditor>hainezob@gmail.com</managingEditor><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 09:48:43 +0100</lastBuildDate><item><guid isPermaLink="false">introduction</guid><link>https://swrith.com/read/introduction</link><title>Introduction</title><description /><a10:updated>2019-12-06T09:48:43+01:00</a10:updated><content:encoded xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">&lt;h2 id="this-first-article-is-going-to-be-a-little-introduction-to-the-blog"&gt;This first &amp;quot;article&amp;quot; is going to be a little introduction to the blog.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, welcome to everyone who made it this far and was enticed to click on this quite odd website.
The content of this blog will only be short stories. A rather oversaturated genre of content you might be saying in front of your screen, but no no no my friend, there's a catch. (Disclosure: the catch is not so creative, but it is still one!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each of the stories will be set in specific universes, don't worry though, there will be multiple of them.
So there might be a &amp;quot;Fantasy blood &amp;amp; gore&amp;quot; universe, where stories with that tag will be somehow linked to the other. Think of it as multiple MCU. I'll try to be as diverse as possible, allowing sub-genre for each universe, even though some of them will be more prone to horror, to fantasy or to plain fiction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll try my best to upload content at least once a week on Saturday, but keep an eye on the site or the &lt;a href="/rss.xml"&gt;RSS feed&lt;/a&gt; as there might be some surprises during the week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you'll have a really good time reading my short stories, and don't be afraid to send me some kind words at hainezob@gmail.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>